

#### **About Me**

I am an aspiring developer currently in my first professional role as a .NET Trainee Developer, where I've gained experience in API development, database integration and management, and cloud deployment through Azure. As part of my responsibilities, I have implemented CI/CD pipelines in Azure to automate and optimize the deployment workflow.

I have earned my Azure AZ-900 certification to deepen my understanding of cloud technologies and add value in modern development and deployment environments.

Before joining the tech world, I worked for seven years as a dog trainer, and in the last year, I also taught in this field. Thanks to this experience, I developed essential skills for teamwork, effective communication, and problem-solving, which I now apply in my role as a developer.



# CONTACT

1123837852

mauro.repetto@hotmail.com

Villa Ballester, Gran Buenos Aires.

-----



## **EDUCATION**

## **Instituto de Formacion Tecnica Superior**

**Software Development Associate's Degree** 

• 2023-Present

#### High School Education José Hernandez High School

Finished 2014

# MAURO REPETTO ANGELICO

BACKEND DEVELOPER AZ-900 CERTIFIED



## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Backend Developer**

KopiusTech 2024-Present

- Api REST
- CI/CD
- Version Control
- Entity Framework
- Jira/Azure Devops

#### **Founder**

Inpu Adiestramiento, Jun 2016 - Present

· Personalized dog training service

#### Dog training instructor

Centro Medico Escuela, May 2022 - Jul 2023

- Instructor overseeing multiple dog training courses.
- Maintaining documentation for students enrolled in the course under my supervision
- •Handling the collection of fees.
- Issuance of certificates.



# **COURSES / LANGUAGES**

#### **English**

Advanced (C2)

#### **Azure Fundamentals Certification (Az-900)**

Microsoft, 2023

#### **Javascript**

CoderHouse, 2022.

#### Fullstack Node.js

Codo a Codo 4.0, 2023.

#### C# Basic

Fundamentals and Logic of Programming MaxiPrograma.com, 2023.

#### **C# Intermediate**

Winforms, .Net Framework, OOP, SQLServer. MaxiPrograma.com, 2023.

#### C# Advanced

Webforms, ASP.Net, Bootstrap. MaxiPrograma.com, 2024.